let questions = [{
        numb: 1,
        question: "	Which of the following are not Java keywords ?",
        answer: "then",
        options: [
            "native",
            "double",
            "volatilee",
            "then"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 2,
        question: "What feature of OOP has a super-class sub-class concept?",
        answer: "Hierarchical inheritance",
        options: [
            "Hierarchical inheritance",
            "Single inheritance",
            "Multiple inheritances",
            "Multilevel inheritance"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 3,
        question: " Modulus operator (%) can be applied to which of these?",
        answer: "Both A and B",
        options: [
            "integers",
            "Floating - point numbers",
            "Both A and B",
            "None of These"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 4,
        question: "What is garbage collection in the context of Java?",
        answer: "Memory used by the object with no reference is automatically reclaimed.",
        options: [
            "Memory used by the object with no reference is automatically reclaimed.",
            "Java deletes all unused java files on the system.",
            "The JVM cleans output of Java program with error.",
            "Any unused package in a program automatically gets deleted."
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 5,
        question: "java also known as ?",
        answer: "Oak",
        options: [
            "Oak",
            "Tree",
            "jquery",
            "none of these"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Which environment variable is used to set the java path?",
        answer: "JAVA_HOME",
        options: [
            "MAVEN_Path",
            "JavaPATH",
            "JAVA",
            "JAVA_HOME"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "What is not the use of “this” keyword in Java?",
        answer: "Passing itself to the method of the same class",
        options: [
            "Referring to the instance variable when a local variable has the same name",
            "Passing itself to the method of the same class",
            "Passing itself to another method",
            "Calling another constructor in constructor chaining"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "What is Truncation in Java?",
        answer: " Floating-point value assigned to an integer type",
        options: [
            "Floating-point value assigned to a Floating type",
            "Floating-point value assigned to an integer type",
            "Integer value assigned to floating type",
            " Integer value assigned to floating type"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Which exception is thrown when java is out of memory?",
        answer: "OutOfMemoryError",
        options: [
            "MemoryError",
            "OutOfMemoryError",
            "MemoryFullException",
            "MemoryOutOfBoundsException"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Which of the following is a superclass of every class in Java?",
        answer: " Object class",
        options: [
            "ArrayList",
            "Abstract class",
            " Object class",
            " String"
        ]
    },


];